dealoz.com 2018-12-23

# DealOz.com Privacy Policy

**DEALOZ.COM PRIVACY STATEMENT**

DealOz.com is committed to your privacy.  
DealOz.com has agreed to notify you of: 

  1. What personally identifiable information of yours or third party personally identification is collected from you through the web site
  2. The organization collecting the information
  3. How the information is used
  4. With whom the information may be shared
  5. What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information
  6. The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under (Name of the Company) control
  7. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information. 

If you feel that this company is not abiding by its posted privacy policy, you should contact our Privacy Department at Contact Us. 

**Information Collection and Use**

DealOz.com is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. DealOz.com collects information from the users at several different points on the web site. 

**Registration**

Users are not required to register in order to use this web site. Users only need to register when they wish to participant in the Forums portion of our website.

The registration form requires users to provide contact information (such as name and email address) and demographic information (such as zip code). The customer's contact information is used to contact the visitor when we send e-mail updates on services and offers available to DealOz.com users. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings. 

**Cookies**

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site. 

Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set advertisements on our site. 

**Contests and Sweepstakes**

When DealOz.com runs contests and sweepstakes on the site, we ask those who enter for certain personal and demographic information (such as your address) so that we can contact you if necessary. In most cases, we will need to know your true identity. The exact rules of each contest will be posted and may vary from contest to contest. When users give us prior permission to do so, we will share their personal information with a third party for the sole purpose of facilitating the delivery of the prizes when they are supplied by a merchant or manufacturer. 

**Log Files**

DealOz.com servers use log files, which contain IP addresses, browser types, access time to help diagnose problems and to administer our web site, as well as gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

**Sharing**

DealOz.com does not share the information it collects from its users with any third party companies or organizations. 

**Links**

This site contains links to other sites. DealOz.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites. 

Therefore, we highly advise you to carefully review any privacy policies posted on those sites before signing up with, or using them.

DealOz.com does not accept any responsibility for the actions and policies of third-party sites you access. This is in regards to the personal information you have provided to them, or which they obtain through your use of their sites directly and/or through the DealOz.com service.

**Public Forums**

This site makes chat rooms, message boards, and news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and that caution should be exercised when deciding to disclose your personal information.

Only a user's nickname is needed in the chat rooms. 

We do not monitor or screen information disclosed through services such as chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups. 

**Security**

http://www.dealoz.com has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control.

When our registration form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as your password and/or phone number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our registration form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just surfing. To learn more about SSL, follow this link <http://www.godaddy.com/ssl/>. 

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Our employees must use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desk. When they return, they must re-enter their password to re-gain access to your information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Every quarter, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our customers information is protected. Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment, behind a locked cage. 

If you have any questions about the security at our web site, you can send an email to Contact Us. 

**Supplementation of Information**

DealOz.com does not supplement any information we receive from our users with any information from 3rd party sources. 

**Communication/Special Offers**

We send all new members a welcoming email to verify password and username. From time to time the established users may receive information from DealOz.com which the users may find interesting or useful. If a user does not wish to receive this type of information they may unsubscribe from such communications by writing us at Contact Us. 

**Site and Service Updates**

We also send our users site and service announcement updates. Members are not able to un-subscribe from service announcements, which contain important information about the service. These announcements will not contain any promotional or marketing material. We communicate with our users to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account via email. 

**Correct/Update/Delete Personal Information**

If a user personally identifiable information changes (such as your zip code), or if a user no longer desires our service, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove that user personal data provided to us. This can be done by clicking on the "My Account" link at the bottom of the website or by visiting https://www.dealoz.com/price/user/profile or by emailing our Customer Support at Contact Us. 

**Notification of Changes**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. 

**Legal Disclaimer**

We may disclose personal information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law or comply with a legal process served on our Web site

**Contacting DealOz.com**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this web site, contact: 

DealOz Support Team   
DealOz.com   
109 E 17TH ST STE 5273   
Cheyenne WY 82001
